unitedvacations.com 2010-05-07

# Privacy Policy - United Vacations - Protecting the Privacy of Our Customers

**Introduction**  
At United Vacations, we believe that it is extremely important to protect the privacy of our customers. We are providing this privacy policy to help you better understand the ways in which your personal information is gathered and used on the www.unitedvacations.com website.

United Vacations is operated by The Mark Travel Corporation. The Mark Travel Corporation and its affiliated technology and marketing agencies, and travel agency distributors, gather, store, and process the information from the United Vacations website. They help United Vacations use customer information to create and distribute products, specials, promotions, and website features for our customers. _Except as indicated in this Privacy Policy, The Mark Travel Corporation, and their affiliated technology and marketing agencies, and travel agency distributors (hereafter "United Vacations") will not sell or share your personally identifiable information with any third party company or agency without your permission._ If you have any comments or questions regarding this privacy statement, please contact United Vacations via our online Customer service.

                                                                   Back To Top 

**Scope**  
This policy applies to all personal information collected by or submitted to United Vacations online at the United Vacations web site. ****

**Third Party Web Sites Accessible via united.com**  
The unitedvacations.com web site contains links to web sites maintained by third parties. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites. This Privacy Policy covers only the unitedvacations.com site, and does not cover any other site, including those related to this site such as united.com, ual.com or the non-U.S. united.com sites. We have no control over other sites' privacy policies or use of any personal information you or others may share with them. Please do not assume that our Privacy Policy covers those other sites.

Back To Top 

**Information United Vacations Collects**  
The United Vacations website collects customer information in a number of ways: when you sign up to receive emails, when you book online using the United Vacations online booking form, when you fill out a Customer Service request, when you send a comment to the suggestion link on our weekly email, and when you forward an email/webpage to a friend.

The types of information collected on these pages include but are not limited to the following:

      Customer Name  
      Traveling Companion Name  
      Mailing Address  
      Email Address  
      Telephone Number  
      Credit/Debit Card Information  
      Reservation Number  
      Age Range  
      Gender  
      Destination Information Desired  
      Other Information Desired  
      Travel Habits 

Back To Top 

**How Your Information Is Used**  
When you sign up for the United Vacations email guestbook, you have the choice of receiving or not receiving emails. If you choose to receive emails, United Vacations will send you regular emails promoting vacation travel, specials, sales and other information. You may unsubscribe from the email specials list at any time by accessing the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email or by visiting the guestbook sign up page and entering your email address in the [unsubscribe box](http://www.secure02.com/UnitedVacations/consumer_unsub.asp). 

You may also update your profile information at any time when you log in to [My Account](http://res.unitedvacations.com/account/retrievelogin.aspx?ctl=a).

When you sign up for the United Vacations email guestbook or book a vacation online, we collect and share your personal information such as your name, address, phone numbers, and email address, with UAL Corporation, United Air Lines, Inc. and UAL Loyalty Services, Inc. This information is used to process and complete your online order, to ensure that you receive applicable mileage credit for online travel purchases for participating flights and so that United or its partners, affiliates or companies may contact you (by phone, email or regular mail) about services or products that may be of interest to you. United's privacy policy, which may be viewed at [united.com](http://www.united.com/), shall apply to all personal information collected by The Mark Travel Corporation on unitedvacations.com and submitted to UAL Corporation, United Air Lines, Inc. and UAL Loyalty Services, Inc.

The information you supply when you book a vacation online is used to process and complete your online order. When you purchase travel services from United Vacations, we provide information about you to the airline, car rental agency, hotel, travel agency or other contracted third party. This information is necessary to process your request and to ensure the successful fulfillment of your travel arrangements. United Vacations does not share this information with any outside parties except to the extent necessary to process your order (for example, credit card authorizations). Information you submit for the purposes of online bookings will not be used to subscribe you for the email guest book unless you specifically opt-in for the email guestbook by checking the appropriate box on the online booking form.

The information you supply when you send in a Customer Service request is used to assist you with your request. It may also be used to help United Vacations review and improve its products, promotions, and customer service.

The information you supply when you send a suggestion or comment to the email suggestion link is used to reply to your comment. Your information may also be forwarded on to the relevant product team or Customer Service team to further process your comment or to help improve United Vacations product, promotions and customer service.

The information you supply when you send an email/webpage to a friend is used to forward the relevant email or webpage information. United Vacations will not send additional emails or mailings to your friend. Your friend must subscribe to our guestbook or provide information himself/herself through one of the other available means before United Vacations will contact him/her.

Information collected through some/all of the methods listed above may be used by United Vacations to improve products, processes and customer service. United Vacations may also use some/all of the information to create customer mailing lists and may occasionally send our customers promotional pieces or other mailings. Mailing lists compiled from the information you provide will only be used by United Vacations for its own marketing and promotional efforts, and will not be sold or shared with any third parties.

United Vacations may also use non-identifying or aggregate information to improve our website, track promotional success, and/or to share website usage information with our hotel, airline or other business partners. This information may include number of page views, visitor sessions, session length, hits, number of unique visitors, browser type, number of visits by each visitor, most requested pages, most accessed pages, top paths through the site, number of returning users. Not all of this information is shared with our business partners, but some aggregate numbers such as page views on a particular page during a particular time frame may be shared. However, no personally identifiable information about you will be shared with any third party.

Back To Top   

**United Vacations use of IP Addresses and Cookies**  
United Vacations uses cookies to track visitors to our site. United Vacations gathers the number of unique visitors as well as the number of page views each visitor makes. The information is used for promotional and marketing purposes only and in the compilation of web usage reports. The reports generated do not recognize any information specific to your location, or anything specific to your individual machine. Cookies are tiny files that are placed on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies do not extract private or personal information from your computer.

Back To Top   

**United Vacations Commitment to Information Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, there are appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. United Vacations uses SSL (Secure Socket Layers) to encrypt and protect your personal information and understands that this is vital in the exchange of credit card and password information.

Back To Top 

**United Vacations Commitment to Child Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of children is very important to United Vacations. United Vacations does not collect or maintain information from our website from those known to be under 13 years of age. No part of the United Vacations website is designed to attract anyone under the age of 13. When online bookings are made, the ages of children traveling with an adult are collected so that the appropriate hotel room and pricing can be chosen for the reservation. The lowest age range specified on the guestbook sign up form is "18 and under."

Back To Top 

**How to Access or Correct Your Information**  
You can access the personally identifiable information you submitted when you made an online reservation by viewing your password-protected reservation. You will be asked to enter both your reservation number and your password. It is the responsibility of the password holder to take reasonable precautions to protect his/her own password. Do not tell anyone your password or write your password down where it can be viewed by others.

To correct, change, or unsubscribe your email address from the United Vacations guestbook, you can visit the guestbook sign up page and enter your email address in the [unsubscribe box](https://www.secure02.com/UnitedVacations/unsub_trigger.asp). First, unsubscribe your old or incorrect email address. Then if you wish to re-subscribe, return to our guestbook sign up page and enter your new information.

Back To Top 

**Opt-In Information**  
If you wish to receive information about United Vacations news, products, and specials via email, you may sign up on the email specials sign-up page. You may also sign up to receive email specials when you book online by checking the appropriate box on the online booking form. Information you submit for the purposes of online bookings will not be used to subscribe you for the email guest book unless you specifically opt-in for the email guestbook.

Information you submit through any of the online methods, including online booking, may be used to create customer mailing lists. United Vacations may occasionally send its customers promotional pieces or other mailings. Mailing lists compiled from the information you provide will only be used by United Vacations for its own marketing and promotional efforts, and will not be sold or shared with any third parties.

Back To Top 

**Opting Out**  
If you are not interested in receiving either e-mail or other forms of direct marketing, you may choose to "opt out" at such time personal information is collected. The decision not to receive future e-mail communications can be made at any time by "opting out" using the link provided on every email message. Please allow up to 60 days for your name and telephone number to be removed from any marketing programs that are currently underway.

Back To Top 

**Notification of Changes to United Vacations Information-Use Policies**  
If at some future date, United Vacations determines that it will change the manner in which it uses the information it collects on the website, you will be notified prior to United Vacations making the change. You would have the option of choosing to continue or not continue to be a member of the United Vacations database receiving emails, and would have the option of unsubscribing. Information collected prior to any information-use changes would be managed according to the Privacy Policy in place at the time it was collected. Only new information collected online would be subject to any new information-use policies.

Back To Top 

**How to Contact United Vacations**  
If you have any questions or comments regarding the United Vacations privacy policy, please contact United Vacations via online Customer Service.

Back To Top
